objc.io 2015-05-02

# Privacy Policy - objc.io

#### What information do we collect?

We collect anonymous usage statistics when you visit our website or use our mobile application. When you sign up for our newsletter, we store your email address.

#### What do we use your information for?

We use anonymous usage statistics from our website and mobile application to improve our services. When you sign up for our newsletter, we use your email address to inform you about new objc.io issues.

#### Do we use cookies?

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction in order to improve our services in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our services, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may share anonymous usage statistics with potential partners or advertisers in the future.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

#### Children’s Privacy

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### Your Consent

By using our site or mobile application, you consent to our privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on September 20th, 2013.
